Guide to the Jack Anderson papers, 1930-2004 MS2001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Research files, 1975; 1959-2000; MS2001 Series 4; 59.5 Linear Feet 113 document boxes, 3 flat boxes
  - Thomas Dodd, Undated
    - Levine pardon, 1966; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 354, Folder 6)
    - Material copied and returned to Anderson, 1964; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 354, Folder 7)
    - Merry-Go-Round columns about Dodd, 1962-1963; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 354, Folder 8)
    - *The Mighty MITE, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 354, Folder 9)
    - *Other Investigations Dodd has Suppressed, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 355, Folder 1)
    - Pearson and Anderson - notes and memos, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 355, Folder 2)
    - Pearson and Anderson v. Dodd - briefs, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 355, Folder 3)
    - Pearson and Anderson v. Dodd - Court of Appeals Pleadings File, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 355, Folder 4)
    - Pearson and Anderson v. Dodd - Joint Appendix [1 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 355, Folder 5)
    - Pearson and Anderson v. Dodd - Joint Appendix [2 of 2], 1962; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 356, Folder 1)
    - *Personal Use of Campaign Contributions, 1966; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 356, Folder 2)
    - *Portrait of a Senator, 1966; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 356, Folder 3)
    - Senate Investigation into Charges of Misconduct by Dodd - Vol. 1 [1 of 2], 1966; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 356, Folder 4)
    - Senate Investigation into Charges of Misconduct by Dodd - Vol. 1 [2 of 2], 1966; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 356, Folder 5)
    - Senate Investigation into Charges of Misconduct Against Dodd - Vol. 2, 1966; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 356, Folder 6)
    - Senate Investigation into Charges of Misconduct Against Dodd - Vol. 3 [1 of 2], 1966; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 356, Folder 7)
    - Senate Investigation into Charges of Misconduct Against Dodd - Vol. 3 [2 of 2], 1966; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 357, Folder 1)
    - Senate Investigation into Charges of Misconduct Against Dodd - Vol. 4, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 357, Folder 2)
    - Senate Investigation into Charges of Misconduct Against Dodd - Vol. 5, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 357, Folder 3)
  - FBI Files, undated
    - FBI Files -- Abernathy, Ralph [1 of 2], undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R9, Folder 1)
    - FBI Files -- Abernathy, Ralph [2 of 2], undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R9, Folder 2)
    - FBI Files -- Saul Alinsky, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R9, Folder 3)
    - FBI Files -- Anderson, Jack [1 of 2], undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R9, Folder 4)
    - FBI Files -- Anderson, Jack [2 of 2], undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R9, Folder 5)
    - FBI Files -- Baldwin, James, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R10, Folder 1)
    - FBI Files -- Belafonte, Harry, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R10, Folder 2)
    - FBI Files -- Berrigan, Daniel [1 of 2], undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R10, Folder 3)
    - FBI Files -- Berrigan, Daniel [2 of 2], undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R10, Folder 4)
    - FBI Files -- Berrigan, Philip et al., undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R10, Folder 5)
    - FBI Files -- Clay, Cassius [1 of 4], undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R10, Folder 6)
    - FBI Files -- Clay, Cassius [2 of 4], undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R10, Folder 7)
    - FBI Files -- Clay, Cassius [3 of 4], undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R10, Folder 8)
    - FBI Files -- Clay, Cassius [4 of 4], undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R11, Folder 1)
    - FBI Files -- Concerned American Mothers, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R11, Folder 2)
    - FBI Files -- Cuban propaganda, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R11, Folder 3)
    - FBI Files -- Davis, Ossie, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R11, Folder 4)
    - FBI Files -- Davis, Sammy Jr., undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R11, Folder 5)
    - FBI Files -- Dawson, Darrell, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R11, Folder 6)
    - FBI Files -- Fauntroy, Walter, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R11, Folder 7)
    - FBI Files -- Fonda, Jane [1 of 2], undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R11, Folder 8)
    - FBI Files -- Fonda, Jane [2 of 2], undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R11, Folder 9)
    - FBI Files -- Hiss, Alger, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R11, Folder 10)
    - FBI Files -- Hudson, Rock, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R11, Folder 11)
    - FBI Files -- Innis, Roy, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R11, Folder 12)
    - FBI Files -- Jordan, Absalom, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R11, Folder 13)
    - FBI Files -- King, Coretta Scott, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 1)
    - FBI Files -- Kitt, Eartha, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 2)
    - FBI Files -- Louis, Joe, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 3)
    - FBI Files -- Martin, Dean, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 4)
    - FBI Files -- Marx, Groucho, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 5)
    - FBI Files -- McKissick, Floyd, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 6)
    - FBI Files -- Namath, Joe, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 7)
    - FBI Files -- O'Hair, Madalyn Murray, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 8)
    - FBI Files -- Rentzel, Thomas, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 9)
    - FBI Files -- Reuss, Michael, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 10)
    - FBI Files -- Ruby, Jack, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 11)
    - FBI Files -- Spingarn, Stephen, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 12)
    - FBI Files -- Spock, Benjamin, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 13)
    - FBI Files -- Stone, I.F., undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 14)
    - FBI Files -- Welk, Lawrence, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 15)
    - FBI Files -- White House demonstrations, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 16)
    - FBI Files -- Wilkins, Ronald, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 17)
    - FBI Files -- Wilkins, Roy, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box R12, Folder 18)
  - Mow-Hsiang, undated
    - Brandenburg v. Roberts, undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 454, Ledger 2)
    - Mow-Hsiang v. Republic of China, undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 455, Ledger 1)
    - Mow-Hsiang v. Republic of China, undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 455, Ledger 3)
    - Mow-Hsiang v. Republic of China, Law File Number 1, undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 454, Ledger 1)
    - Mow-Hsiang v. Republic of China Law File Number 1, undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 454, Ledger 3)
    - Legal papers pertaining to search of Mow's home, undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 455, Ledger 2)
    - Republic of China v. Pang-Tsu Mow, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 455, Ledger 4)
    - Republic of China v. Standard Parts Corp, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 454, Ledger 4)
    - Accounts of Chiang's activities with Japan and Russia, 1953-1957; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 358, Folder 1)
    - Administration Funds and Revolving Funds Entrusted to Chinese Air Force Office in USA, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 358, Folder 2)
    - Brandenburg v. Roberts correspondence, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 358, Folder 3)
    - Brandenburg v. Roberts, 1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 358, Folder 4)
    - Bureau of Aeronautical Industries Funds Entrusted to Chinese Air Force Office in USA, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 358, Folder 5)
    - Cables between Mow and Chiang Kai-Shek, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 358, Folder 6)
    - Chinese Air Force - aircraft parts, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 358, Folder 7)
    - Chinese Air Force - Balance sheets, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 358, Folder 8)
    - Chinese Air Force - Finance Committee, 1950; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 358, Folder 9)
    - Chinese Air Force - forms, 1949; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 358, Folder 10)
    - Chinese Air Force gasoline purchase, 1948; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 358, Folder 11)
    - Chinese Air Force - Monetary and Property Open Control and Supervisory Committee, 1949; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 358, Folder 12)
    - Chinese Air Force monthly financial reports, 1949; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 359, Folder 1)
    - Chinese Air Force monthly financial reports [1 of 2], 1950; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 359, Folder 2)
    - Chinese Air Force monthly financial reports [2 of 2], 1950; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 359, Folder 3)
    - Chinese Air Force monthly financial reports [1 of 2], 1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 359, Folder 4)
    - Chinese Air Force monthly financial reports [2 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 359, Folder 5)
    - Chinese Air Force - Monthly financial report, 1945; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 360, Folder 1)
    - Chinese Air Force organization chart, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 360, Folder 2)
    - Chinese Air Force Statement of Expenditure, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 360, Folder 3)
    - Detailed Story of Case No. 2, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 360, Folder 4)
    - Documents forged by C.J. Chow for explanation of Case #1, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 360, Folder 5)
    - Documents regarding Case No. 1 and Case No. 2, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 360, Folder 6)
    - Exhibits 1-19, 1950; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 360, Folder 7)
    - Exhibits 6-8 re: $10 million and 3 Manila contracts, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 360, Folder 8)
    - Hau-Tai Trading Co., 1956-1966; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 360, Folder 9)
    - Hsiang v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 360, Folder 10)
    - Hsiang, V.S. - correspondence, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 360, Folder 11)
    - Hsiang deposition [1 of 5], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 361, Folder 1)
    - Hsiang deposition [2 of 5], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 361, Folder 2)
    - Hsiang deposition [3 of 5], 1957; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 361, Folder 3)
    - Hsiang deposition [4 of 5], 1958; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 361, Folder 4)
    - Hsiang deposition [5 of 5], 1959; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 362, Folder 1)
    - Hsiang INS hearing, 1955; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 362, Folder 2)
    - Hsiang legal documents, 1955; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 362, Folder 3)
    - Hsiang, V.S. - tax case [1 of 2], 1958; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 362, Folder 4)
    - Hsiang, V.S. - tax case [2 of 2], 1956-1959; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 362, Folder 5)
    - Immigration documents - V.S. Hsiang, 1950; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 362, Folder 6)
    - Mow, Pang-Tsu, 1957-1962; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 363, Folder 1)
    - Mow correspondence, 1957-1962; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 363, Folder 2)
    - Mow correspondence [1 of 2], 1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 363, Folder 3)
    - Mow correspondence [2 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 363, Folder 4)
    - Mow, P.T. - notes, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 363, Folder 5)
    - Mow-Hsiang affidavits, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 363, Folder 6)
    - Mow-Hsiang biographies, 1952-1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 363, Folder 7)
    - Mow-Hsiang - Brandenburg v. Roberts notes, 1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 363, Folder 8)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - auditor, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 363, Folder 9)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - bank, 1951-1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 364, Folder 1)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - Chinese embassy, 1952-1954; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 364, Folder 2)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - Congressional, 1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 364, Folder 3)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - Custodian reports, 1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 364, Folder 4)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - general, 1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 364, Folder 5)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - general [1 of 2], 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 364, Folder 6)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - general [2 of 2], 1954; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 364, Folder 7)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - general, 1955-1956; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 364, Folder 8)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - general, 1951-1957; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 364, Folder 9)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - general, 1951-1954; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 364, Folder 10)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - Journal, 1951-1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 365, Folder 1)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - Kan, C.H., 1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 365, Folder 2)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - Kisich, Oliver, 1951-1954; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 365, Folder 3)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - Kuo Hwa Yu, 1952-1955; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 365, Folder 4)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - Li Tsung-jen, 1952-1955; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 365, Folder 5)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - Mexican case [1 of 2], 1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 365, Folder 6)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - Mexican case [2 of 2], 1951-1956; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 365, Folder 7)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - Morse, Wayne, 1951-1954; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 365, Folder 8)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - New York bank case, 1950-1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 365, Folder 9)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - Standard Parts Corp., 1951-1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 366, Folder 1)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - State Department, 1951-1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 366, Folder 2)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - Swiss bank, 1951-1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 366, Folder 3)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - United Nations, 1952-1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 366, Folder 4)
    - Mow-Hsiang correspondence - Warren Woods, 1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 366, Folder 5)
    - Mow-Hsiang depositions, 1955; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 366, Folder 6)
    - Mow-Hsiang documents, 1957; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 366, Folder 7)
    - Mow-Hsiang documents, 1949-1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 366, Folder 8)
    - Mow and Hsiang documents, 1951-1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 367, Folder 1)
    - Mow-Hsiang document translations, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 367, Folder 2)
    - Mow-Hsiang document translations [2 of 2], 1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 367, Folder 3)
    - Mow and Hsiang - Hearing before Auditor, 1951-1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 367, Folder 4)
    - Mow-Hsiang law file - The Chinese Journal, 1950-1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 367, Folder 5)
    - Mow-Hsiang law file - District Court, 1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 368, Folder 1)
    - Mow-Hsiang law file - memoranda and notes, 1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 368, Folder 2)
    - Mow-Hsiang law file - memoranda and notes [1 of 2], 1952-1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 368, Folder 3)
    - Mow-Hsiang law file - memoranda and notes [2 of 2], 1952-1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 368, Folder 4)
    - Mow-Hsiang law file - Mexican case [1 of 3], 1952-1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 368, Folder 5)
    - Mow-Hsiang law file - Mexican case [2 of 3], 1952-1954; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 368, Folder 6)
    - Mow-Hsiang law file - Mexican case [3 of 3], 1952-1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - Mow-Hsiang law file - Standard Parts Corp., 1955-1956; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 369, Folder 2)
    - Mow-Hsiang law file - Supreme Court, 1948; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 369, Folder 3)
    - Mow-Hsiang news clippings and photos, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 369, Folder 4)
    - Mow receipts, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 369, Folder 5)
    - Mow and Hsiang v. Republic of China - Official briefs and petitions, 1950; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 369, Folder 6)
    - Mow - rough notes and extra copies, 1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 370, Folder 1)
    - Mow's trip to Formosa, 1948-1950; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 370, Folder 2)
    - Mow-Hsiang translation, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 370, Folder 3)
    - Procurement Funds Entrusted to Chinese Air Force Office in USA, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 370, Folder 4)
    - Procurement Funds Entrusted to Chinese Air Force in USA, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 370, Folder 5)
    - Purchase of Aviation Gasoline by Chinese Nationalist Government, 1949-1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 370, Folder 6)
    - Radar project, 1948-1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 371, Folder 1)
    - Record of documents forwarded to attorney, 1958-1959; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 371, Folder 2)
    - Refutation to the Charges Leveled Against Mow, 1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 371, Folder 3)
    - Republic of China vs. Mow and Hsiang, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 371, Folder 4)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang Vol. 1 [1 of 3], 1952-1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 371, Folder 5)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang Vol. 1 [2 of 3], 1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 371, Folder 6)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang Vol. 1 [3 of 3], 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 371, Folder 7)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang Vol. 2, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 372, Folder 1)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang Vol. 3-4, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 372, Folder 2)
    - Republic of China v. Mow-Hsiang Vol. 5-6, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 372, Folder 3)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang Vol. 7-8, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 372, Folder 4)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang Vol. 9-11, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 372, Folder 5)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang Vol. 12-13, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 373, Folder 1)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang Vol. 14-15, 1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 373, Folder 2)
    - Republic of China v. Mow et al. - depositions, 1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 373, Folder 3)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - deposition of Liang Chien Cha [1 of 2], 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 373, Folder 4)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - deposition of Liang Chien Cha [2 of 2], 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 373, Folder 5)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - deposition of Pao-Hua Cheng, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 373, Folder 6)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - deposition of Luis Corea, 1956; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 373, Folder 7)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - deposition of Tienn Chen Fang, 1956; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 373, Folder 8)
    - Republic of China v. Mow et al. - Deposition of V.S. Hsiang [1 of 3], 1956; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 374, Folder 1)
    - Republic of China v. Mow et al. - Deposition of V.S. Hsiang [2 of 3], 1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 374, Folder 2)
    - Republic of China v. Mow et al. - Deposition of V.S. Hsiang [3 of 3], 1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 374, Folder 3)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - Deposition of Robert Keiner, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 374, Folder 4)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - deposition of Chung-Kwang Liu, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 374, Folder 5)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - deposition of David Shuen, 1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 374, Folder 6)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - deposition of K.C. Tsao, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 374, Folder 7)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - deposition of K.H. Yu, 1952-1954; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 375, Folder 1)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - deposition of Michael Y.A. Yu, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 375, Folder 2)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - documents, 1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 375, Folder 3)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - motions and complaints, 1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 375, Folder 4)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - official briefs and appendices [1 of 4], 1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 375, Folder 5)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - official briefs and appendices [2 of 4], 1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 375, Folder 6)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - official briefs and appendices [3 of 4], 1956-1957; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 376, Folder 1)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - official briefs and appendices [4 of 4], 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 376, Folder 2)
    - Republic of China v. Mow and Hsiang - Treasury Bill Action, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 376, Folder 3)
    - Republic of China v. Standard Parts Corp. Vol. 1, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 376, Folder 4)
    - Republic of China v. Standard Parts Corp. Vol. 2, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 376, Folder 5)
    - Republic of China v. Standard Parts Corporation - deposition of William A. Roberts [1 of 2], 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 377, Folder 1)
    - Republic of China v. Standard Parts Corporation - deposition of William A. Roberts [2 of 2], 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 377, Folder 2)
    - Republic of China v. Standard Parts Corporation - deposition of Warren Woods [1 of 2], 1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 377, Folder 3)
    - Republic of China v. Standard Parts Corporation - deposition of Warren Woods [2 of 2], 1951; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 377, Folder 4)
    - Republic of China v. Standard Parts Corporation - examinations, 1950; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 377, Folder 5)
    - Supplement to Exhibit 19-1, 1960-2004; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 377, Folder 6)
    - Synopsis of P-51 case, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 377, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1960-1966; 1960-2004; MS2001 Series 5; 10 Linear Feet 20 document boxes
  This series primarily contains Anderson's incoming correspondence, though there is a small quantity of outgoing correspondence. It dates from 1960 to 2004, and correspondence from the early years also includes some letters to and from Drew Pearson, Anderson's predecessor on the Merry-Go-Round column. It is arranged first by type of correspondence (e.g. reader correspondence, research correspondence, correspondence with colleagues, personal correspondence) and then chronologically. Unless the envelopes contained unique and relevant information about letter writers, they have been removed.
  Reader correspondence contains letters sent by readers of the Merry-Go-Round column commenting on Anderson's writing, proposing stories, or requesting his help to call attention to their problems. (A small quantity of these letters remain unopened.) Research correspondence contains letters written to Anderson from sources and reporters regarding story ideas. Other correspondence includes: correspondence with colleagues; correspondence about Anderson's books, TV, and film projects; invitations and thank-you notes; and personal correspondence from Anderson's friends and Mormon church acquaintances. Correspondence is found elsewhere in the collection as well, when it specifically relates to corollary material and was originally found with that material. A few items have been restricted because the writer indicated a desire to remain a confidential source.
  This series has three subseries: Reader correspondence, Research correspondence, and Other correspondence.
  Reader correspondence is arranged chronologically. Research correspondence is also arranged chronologically. Other correspondence is arranged first by type of correspondence and then chronologically.
  - Reader correspondence, 1967
    - Reader correspondence, 1968-1969; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 237, Folder 1)
    - Reader correspondence, 1970; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 237, Folder 2)
    - Reader correspondence, 1971; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 237, Folder 3)
    - Reader correspondence, 1972; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 237, Folder 4)
    - Reader correspondence, 1973; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 237, Folder 5)
    - Reader correspondence, 1974; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - Reader correspondence, 1975; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 238, Folder 2)
    - Reader correspondence, 1975; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - Reader correspondence [1 of 2], 1976; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 238, Folder 4)